

613-413-8866
yidahou@gmail.com
https://yidahou.com/final-portfolio/

As an experienced UI/UX Designer, I care about details both visually and functionally and consider simple yet effective affordances matters. I have delivered several successful products to the market. I also always look to learn new things.

# **Skills**



## **Education**

Algonquin College

2020 - 2021



Interactive Media Design
Dean's honours list | GPA 3.93

Nanchang Institute of Tech.

2002 — 2005



**Digital Web Design** 

## **Hobbies**

Traveling, Hiking, Cooking, Meditation.

# **Experience**

- RideShark Corporation. / UI/UX designer

2021/5- present

(Ottawa, Canada)

- Defined new style guidelines and redesigned SaaS dashboard.
- Conduct user research, defined users needs, pain points, jobs-to-be-done, created low/high-fedility wireframes.
- Conducted qualitative usability testing to uncover opportunities to solve problems.
- Collaborated with developers, product managers to deliver designs from scratch.
- Xinhua Yuntu Tech. Co.,Ltd / Senior UI / Graphic Designer

2014/5-2017/5

(Bejing, China)

- In charge of the typography design for the monthly magazine.
- Designed new product and features from scratch. Launched online successfully.
- Collaborated with engineers to maintain the official website update
- Created all of the branding and visual styles as well as coached designer team to refine the visual details.

#### Youzhong Network. / Senior UI/UX Designer

2011/4-2014/4

(Beijing, China)

- Conducted market research and ideated with product managers, designed new features and numerous visual effects for website desktop, iOS devices.
- Collaborated with engineers to launch new features on time.

### — China Vision Media Group Limited. / Graphic Designer

2010/5-2011/3

(Beijing, China)

Designed numerous graphic (Logos, brochures, posters, banners). Created banners for mobile / TV end, gathered feedback and collaborated with engineers for debugging.